Guide to the Dorothy Schefer Faux fashion collection, 1931-2017.
Faux, Dorothy Schefer fashion collection
- Fashion publications
  - Books, 1987-2006
    - The Dale Sko Hack: Exploring Modes of Production and Re-Form Tactics and The Dale Sko Hack, Design Management: A Reinterpretation, a lecture at Istanbul Technical University, 2006; BOOK 2; von Busch, Otto (Box 17)
      The Dale Sko Hack: Exploring Modes of Production and Re-Form Tactics and The Dale Sko Hack, Design Management: A Reinterpretation, a lecture at Istanbul Technical University, 4 May 2006, on the theme of Modes of Production and Design Hacking, by Otto von Busch and Karl Palmas. [Published by Nordisk Kunstnarsenter Dalsasen, n.d.?]
    - Geoffrey Beene Unbound, 1994; BOOK 3; Mirabella, Grace; Beene, Geoffrey (Box 22)
      Interview by Grace Mirabella, published in conjunction with the exhibition Geoffrey Beene Unbound, The Museum at the Fashion Institute of Technology, February 14-April 30, 1994.
    - The Fifteenth Annual Council of Fashion Designers of America Awards, 1995; BOOK 4; Council of Fashion Designers of America (Box 19)
      Awards show program/catalog. Designers/celebreties awarded or mentioned include: Ralph Lauren, Tommy Hilfiger, Marie-Anne Oudejans for Tocca, Richard Tyler, Richard Bengtsson and Edward Pavlick for Richard Edwards, Kate Spade, Hush Puppies, Tom Ford for Gucci, Suzy Menkes, Isaac Mizrahi and Douglas Keeve, Robert Isabell, Lauren Bacall, Hubert de Givenchy, and Bill Blass.
    - Spun: Bangkok Fashion Now & Tomorrow, vol. 4, 2005; BOOK 5; Bangkok Fashion City | Ministry of Industry, Bangkok (Box 19)
      Contains several fabric samples.
    - The Collection of Geoffrey Beene, 2005; BOOK 6; Beene, Geoffrey; Sotheby's (Box 19)
      Auction took place on September 23-24, 2005
    - Emanuel Ungaro, 1992; BOOK 7; Weill, Alain; Gruppo GTF (Box 19)
      Includes essays by Federico Fellini, Katia D. Kaupp, Yves Navarre, and Helene de Turckheim
    - Seven Designers in Monogram, 1995; BOOK 8; Louis Vuitton Malletier (Box 19)
      Designers include: Azzedine Alaia, Manolo Blahnik, Romeo Gigli, Helmut Lang, Isaac Mizrahi, Sybilla, and Vivienne Westwood.
    - Beauty: The Twentieth Century, 2000; BOOK 10; Faux, Dorothy Schefer; Universe Publishing (Box 19)
      Includes essays by Nathalie Chahine, Catherine Jazdzewski, Marie-Pierre Lannelongue, Francoise Mohrt, Fabienne Rousso, and Francine Vormese
    - Self Passage: collected methods/a cookbook 2003-2004, 2005; BOOK 11; von Busch, Otto (Box 19)
    - Sex & Power, 1987; BOOK 13; Newton, Helmut; Xavier Moreau Inc. (Box 19)
      vol. 1, no. 1
    - The Designers, 1996; BOOK 14; Saks Fifth Avenue (Box 19)
      Designers included are: Dolce & Gabbana, Givenchy, Yves Saint Laurent Rive Gauche, Romeo Gigli, Missoni, Gianfranco Ferre, Emanuel Ungaro Parallele, Thierry Mugler, John Galliano, Bill Blass, Giorgio Armani, Chanel, Ralph Lauren Collection, Prada, Jil Sander, Mary McFadden, Gucci, Lagerfeld, Claude Montana, Christian Louboutin, Christian Lacroix, Ocimar Versolato, Richard Tyler, Badgley Mischka, Issey Miyake, Herve Leger, Isaac Mizrahi, Gianni Versace, Valentino Boutique, Oscar de la Renta, Zoran, Geoffrey Beene, Calvin Klein Collection, Judith Leiber, Jean Paul Gaultier, Sonia Rykiel, Donna Karan, Escada Couture, Moschino Couture, Marie Gray for St. John, Vera Wang, and Carolina Herrera.
    - Beene 30 Years, Undated; BOOK 15; Martin, Richard (Box 22)
      Wit, Fashion and Fabric, with essay by Richard Martin [exhibit catalog?, Costume Institute, Metropolitan Museum of Art?]
    - Black: Colour and Light-3, 1991; BOOK 15; Chanel (Box 22)
    - Blue: Colour and Light-4, 1991; BOOK 16; Chanel (Box 22)
    - Fitness: The American Legacy: Fifty Years in the Fitness Revolution, 1990; BOOK 19; Szekely, Deborah; Diehl, Digby; The Lantz Office (Box 19)
    - Miss Dior, Christian Dior, Paris, 1993; BOOK 20; Christian Dior (Box 19)
      Press kit for Miss Dior perfume, with catalog, 5 color photographs, letter from Regina Kulik, Director, Public Relations, to Dorothy Schefer, Mirabella Magazine, July 15, 1993, and price list, all in pocket folder-style slipcase
    - White: Colour and Light-2, 1991; BOOK 21; Chanel (Box 22)
    - O Wonderful, wonderful and most wonderful, wonderful! And yet again wonderful ...: Portraits of Our U.S. Olympic Hopefuls, 1991; BOOK 73; Arnell, Peter; Sidney Press (Box 19)
      For an exhibition of photographs by Peter Arnell, commissioned by Bausch & Lomb, sponsor of the 1992 Olympic Games.
    - Vicuna, 2008; Loro Piana (Box 34)
  - Visionaire, 1993-2005
    - Visionaire #9, Faces, Summer 1993; VIS 1 (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Ruben Toledo, Mats Gustafson, Francois Berthould, Stephanie Sednaoui, Victoria Bartlett, Alaxandre De Betak, Ann Demeulemeester, Raymond Meirer, Michel Haddi, Bernard Figueroa, Filip Pagowski, Carlos Aponte, Antoine Angruny, Haide, Dwight Marshall, Michael Economy, Bruce Weber, Mario Testino, Satoshi Saikusa, Patrick Robyn, Josef Astor, Orlando Pita, Lou Salvatori, Anh Duong, Ward, Steen Sundland, Anders Wenngren, Andrew Brucker, Andres Serrano, Mika Mizutani, Gregory Foley, Martin Margiela, Steven Klein, Karen Park, Jean-Paul Goude, David Seidner, James White, Stevan Dohar, Michael Capotosto, Mei Tao, Ken Siman, Dovanna Pagowska, Kareem Iliya, Kristina Colovic, Geoffroy de Boismenu, Malcolm Hill, Seta Niland, Peter Robathan, Mark Gagnon, John Newsom, Kevin Mackintosh, Scott Lifschutz, Giana de Johnette, John Scarisbrick, Antonio Lopez, Retamar, Margess Khosrowshahi
    - Visionaire #18, Fashion Special, Fall1 1996; VIS 2; Vuitton, Louis (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Alexander McQueen, Steven Klein, Anna Sui, Dietmar, Azzedine Alaia, Jean-Paul Goude, Bernadette Corporation, Chris Moore, Calvin Klein, Richard Martin, Chanel, John Scarisbrick, Christian Blanken, Christophe Rihet, Christian Lacroix, Carter Smith, Comme Des Carcons, Craigh McDean & M/M, Daryl K, Van Lamsweerde/Matadin, Donna Karan, Luis Sanchis, Elsa Peretti, Miles Aldridge, Eric Bergere, Martine Houghton, Geoffrey Beene, Mario Sorrenti, Giorgio Armani, Mei Tao, Gucci, Hiroshi Tanabe, Helmut Lang, Nan Goldin, Hussein Chalayan, Jurgen Teller, Isaac Mizrahi, Larry Fink, Isabel Toledo, Ruven Afanador, Istante by Versace, Jamil GS, Jean Colonna, Ellen Von Unwerth, Jean-Paul Gaultier, Masha Calloway, John Bartlett, Terry Richardson, John Galliano, Satoshi Saikusa, Junya Watanabe, Arthur Elgort, Kon Tatsuno, Alexi Tan, Marc Jacobs, Jack Pierson, Martin Margiela, Drew Jarrett, Martine Sitbon, Donald Milne, Nike, Wah, Owen Gaster, Stephane Sednaoui, Patricia Field, Ellen Von Unwerth, Prada, Adam Pollina, Ralph Lauren, Joshua Jordan, Richard Edwards, Shinichiro Arakawa, Hiromix, Stephen Sprouse, Jerome Albertino, Susan Cianciolo, Marcelo Krasilcic, Todd Oldham, Enrique Badulescu, Veronique Leroy, Francesca Sorrenti, Viktor & Rolf, Vivienne Westwood, Ruben Toledo, Yohji Yamamoto, Nathaniel Goldberg, Yves Saint Laurent, Mario Testino
    - Visionaire #19, Beauty, Date unknown; VIS 3 (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Glenn O'Brien, Mario Testino, Ellen Von Unwerth, Jean-Paul Goude, Bruce Weber, Peter Lindbergh, Nan Goldin, Cindy Sherman, Mary Ellen Mark, Mats Gustafson, Francois Berthoud, Ruben Toledo, Serge Lutens, Francois Nars, Dick Page, Danilo, Kevyn Aucoin, Topolino, Mathu & Zaldy, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Terry Richardson, Carter Smith, Michael Thompson, Dietmar, Helena Christensen, Nathaniel Goldberg, Miles Aldridge, Janet Beller, Kareem Iliya, Francois Rotger, Patrick McCarthy, Christophe Kutner, Eric Traore, Scott Ewalt, Viktor & Rolf, Mei Tao, Bettina Komenda
    - Visionaire's Fashion 2000: Designers at the Turn of the Millennium, 1997; VIS 9; Gan, Stephen; Browne, Alix; Universe Publishing (Box 19)
      Includes designs byAzzedine Alaia, Victor Alfaro, Adeline Andre, Giorgio Armani, John Barlett, Geoffrey Beene, Richard Bengtsson and Edward Pavlick, Antonio Berardi, Eric Bergere, Bernadette Corporation, Dirk Bikkembergs, Manolo Blahnik, Christian Blanken, Liza Bruce, Hussein Chalayan, Susan Cianciolo, Suzanne Clements and Inacio Ribeiro, Robert Clergerie, Jean Colonna, Alessandro dell'Acqua, Ann Demeulemeester, Domenico Dolce and Stefano Gabbana, Tom Ford, John Galliano, Valentino Garavani, Owen Gaster, Jean-Paul Gaultier, Romeo Gigli, Katharine Hamnett, Viktor Horsting and Rolf Snoeren, Marc Jacobs, Betsey Johnson, Donna Karan, Rei Kawakubo, Dayl Kerrigan, Calvin Klein, Michael Kors, Christian Lacroix, Karl Lagerfeld, Helmut Lang, Ralph Lauren, Herve Leger, Veronique Leroy, Julien MacDonald, Martin Margiela, Alexander McQueen, Issey Miyake, Isaac Mizrahi, Thierry Mugler, Todd Oldham, Rifat Ozbek, Carol Christian Poell, Miuccia Prada, Yves Saint Laurent, Jil Sander, Martine Sitbon, Paul Smith, Stephen Sprouse, Anna Sui, Sybilla, Koji Tatsuno, Isabel Toledo, Philip Treacy, Richard Tyler, Dries Van Noten, Gianni Versace, Junya Watanabe, Vivienne Westwood, and Yohji Yamamoto
    - Visionaire #20, Comme des Garcons, 1997; VIS 4; Kawakubo, Rei (Box 5)
      Includes designs by Bruce Weber, Peter Lindbergh, Karl Lagerfeld, Inez van Lamsweerde, Vinoodh Matadin, Nick Knight, Alexander McQueen, Martin Margiela, Craig McDean & M/M, Mario Sorrenti, Philip-Lorca DiCorcia, Paolo Roversi, Steven Klein, Michael Thompson, Miles Aldridge, Stephane Marais, Julien D'ys, Masayuki Hayashi, Richard Burbridge, Marc Atlan, Joe McKenna, Elisabeth Djian, Alexandra White, Andrew Richardson, Katy England, Eric Wright, Mako Yamazaki, Kishin Shinoyama, Tsuguya Inoue
    - Visionaire #21, Deck of Cards/ The Diamond Issue, Spring 1997; VIS 5 (Box 2)
      Includes designs by Karl Lagerfeld, Mario Testino, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Bruce Weber, Enrique Badulescu, Terry Richardson, Sean Ellis, Steven Klein, Ruben Toledo, David Lachapelle, Mark Mattock, Pamela Hanson, Ellen von Unwerth, Peter Hurst, Carine Roitfeld, Anne Christensen, Kate Roberts, Andrew Richardson, Isabella Blow, Victoria Bartlett, Justin Laurie, Judy Blame, Lori Goldstein, Paul Sinclaire, Matt Jones, Lee Swillingham, Stuart Spalding, Michael Amzalag, Mathias Augustyniak, Fabien Baron
    - Visionaire #22, Chic, 1997; VIS 6; Testino, Mario (Box 2)
      Includes designs by Azzedine Alaia, Alexandre de Paris, Beatrice Amaga, Richard Avedon, Enrique Dabulescu, Balthus, Fabien Baron, Victoria Bartlett, Betty Bee, Eric Bergere, Francois Berthold, Evangeline Blahnik, Manolo Blahnik, Bill Blass, Isabella Blow, Hamish Bowles, Richard Buckley, Paul Cavaco, Suzanne Clements & Inacio Ribeiro, Catherine Deneuve, Philip-Lorca diCorcia, Sean Ellis, Fabric Frontline, Victoria Fernandez, Charles Firmin-Didot, Tom Ford, Leonard Freed, Ivan de la Fressange, Banjamin Galopin, Joyce George, Oberto Gili, Nan Goldin, Wendy Goodman, Mats Gustafson, Fancois Halard, Michael Howells, Lawrence Hull, Lauren Hutton, Kim Inglinsky, Marc Jacobs, Sarah Jones, Stephen Jones, Steven Klein, Harumi Klossowski, Christian Lacroix, Francoise Lacroix, Karl Lagerfeld, Helmut Lang, Brigitte Langevin, Sergio Larrain, David Lasnet, Pierre Le-Tan, Christian Louboutin, Thomas Lenthal, Peter Lindberg, Petra Lindblad, Marc Lopez, Madonna, Matthew Marks, Mark Mattock, Stella McCartney, Joe McKenna, Raymond Meirer, Angela Missoni, Isaac Mizrahi, Sarah Moon, Kate Moss, Lawrence Mynott, Helmut Newton, Camilla Nickerson, Thomas Nutzl, Mariana Ochs, Karla Otto, Maureen Paley, Mr. Pearl, Tom Pechuex, Graziela Peres, Isabelle Peyrut, Paloma Picasso, Hiluz del Priore, Laudonia Pucci, Raucci/Santamaria, Tuca Reines, Andrew Richardson, Terry Richardson, Peter Robathan, Carine Roitfeld, Nicola Rositani, Clara Saint, Yves Saint Laurent, Carole Schulze, Elfie Semotan, Bianca Sforni, Cindy Sherman, David Sims, Paul Smith, Smythson of Bond Street, Solstiss, Franca Sozzani, Luca Stoppini, Tim Street-Porter, David Strettell & Magnum Photos, Anna Sui, Lee Swillingham, Stella Tennant, Paula Thomas, Wolfgang Tillmans, Larry Towell, Tessa Traeger, Inez Van Lamsweede & Vinoodh Matadin, Carmen Mayrink Veiga, Donatella Versace, Gianni Versace, Neville Wakefield, Duncan Ward, Melanie Ward, Bruce Weber, Adam Whitehead, Christopher Wool
    - Visionaire #23, The Emperor's New Clothes, Date unknown; VIS 7; Largerfeld, Karl (Box 6)
    - Visionaire #24, Light, 1998; VIS 8; Ford, Tom (Box 7)
      Includes designs by Christopher Bucklow, Christopher Giglio, Paul Graham, Andreas Gursky, Hiromix, Roni Horn, Toyo Ito, Lee Jenkins, Craig Kalpakjian, Nick Knight, Alexander McQueen, Raymond Meirer, Hayao Miyazaki, Phil Poynter, Thomas Ruff, Luis Sanchis, Peter Saville, John Schabel, Alyson Shotz, Sam Taylor-Wood, Mario Testino, Wolfgang Tillmans, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Viktor & Rolf, Jane & Louise Wilson
    - Visionaire #25, Visionary, 1998; VIS 9 (Box 8)
      Includes designs by Craig McDean, Junya Watanabe by Mario Sorrenti & Jane How, Comme des Garcons by David Lasnet & Peter Robathan & Terry Richardson & Miles Aldridge, Mario Testino & Carine Roitfeld, Mats Gustafson, Yohji Yamamoto by Karl Lagerfeld, Martin Margiela & Hermes by Bettina Komenda & Jean-louis Dumas-Hermes, Philip-Lorca diCorcia, Christian Lacroix by John Akehurst, Eiko Ishioka, Yves Saint Laurent by Francois Nars, Fabien Baron, John Galliano & Christian Dior by Ellen Von Unwerth, Twyla Tharp by Isabel Toledo & Ruben Toledo, Alexander McQueen & Givenchy by Horst Diekgerdes & Camille Bidault-Waddington, Ann Demeulemeester & Prada & Jil Sander & Martin Sitbon by Francois Berthoud, Jeremy Scott by Sean Ellis & Isabella Blow, Helmut Lang, Philip Treacy by Marcus Tomlinson, Husseun Chalayan by Luis Sanchis, Oliver Theyskens by Satoshi Saikusa & Mika Mizutani, David Bowie presents artists Beth B & Gavin Turk & Tracey Emin & Tony Oursler, Marc Jacobs & Louis Vuitton by Marc Hom featuring artists Oliver Herring & Leonardo Drew & Elliot Puckette & Tracey Moffatt, New Vision by Raf Simons & Antonio Berardi & Veronique Branquinho & Nicolas Ghesquiere for Balenciaga, New Vision by Erik Halley & Julien Macdonald & Bless & Veronique Leroy, Viktor & Rolf by Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Towa Tei
    - Visionaire #26, Fantasy, 1998; VIS 10 (Box 9)
      Includes designs by Inez van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Mario Testino, Carine Roitfeld, Christian Lacroix, Nick Knight, Issac Mizrahi, Manolo Blahnik, Steven Klein, David Byrhe, Adelle Lutz, Jack Pierson, Andres Serrano, Serge Lutens, Tim Burton & Lisa Marie, Terry Richardson, David Seidner, Jessye Norman, Stephane Sednaoui, Carter Smith, Richard Burbridge, Josef Astor, Javier Vallhonrat, Christophe Rihet, Anuschka Blommers & Niels Schumm, Mark Morris, Jeff Wall, Dan Graham, Tony Oursler, Todd Haynes, Sylvie Fleury, Elliott Puckette, Gregory Crewdson, Oliver Wasow, Viktor & Rolf, Jeremy Scott, Nicolas Ghesquiere for Balenciago, Topolino, Eric Traore, Laurie Simmons, Quay Brothers, Patrick Kinmonth, Tessa Traeger, Dai Rees, Kevin Summers, Lee Jenkins, Raf Simmons, Bert Houbrechts, Christopher Moore, Thomas Nutzl, Miwa Yanagr, Thom Lussier, Andrew Richardson, Havana Laffitte, Paul Stura, Lee Wood, Lionel Bouard, Barbara Turk, Marie-Amelie Sauve, Michel Botbol, Dennis Freedman, David Hazan, Hermes
    - Visionaire #27, Movement, 1999; VIS 11 (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Matt Atlas & Marcus Piggott, Hussein Chalayan, Fabien Baron, Ross Bleckner, Francois Berthould, Victoria Bartlett, WK Eddy Desplanques, Nick Knight, Steven Klein, Sean Ellis, Katy England, Alex Conzalez, Chris Levine, Steven Meisel, Alexander McQueen, Martin Margiela, Raul Martinez, Marcus Mam, J. Abbott Miller & Paul Carlos, Tony Oursler, Tony Payne, Thierry Perez, Mario Testino, Marcus Tomlinson, Karl Templer, Peter Saville, Jeremy Scott
    - Visionaire #28, The Bible, 1999; VIS 12 (Box 4)
    - Visionaire #29, Woman, 1999; VIS 13 (Box 1)
      Includes designs by Nick Knight, Mario Testino, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, David Bowie, Karl Lagerfeld, John Galliano, Paolo Roversi, Nan Goldin, Peter Lindbergh, Hussein Chalayan, Francesco Clemente, Stella McCartney, Steven Klein, Cindy Sherman, Vanessa Beecroft, Nobuyoshi Araki, Serge Lutens, David Bradshaw, Mats Gustafson, Francois Berthoud, Miles Aldridge, Steve Hiett, Terry Richardson, Sean Ellis, Carter Smith, Ellen Von Unwerth, Marcus Tomlinson, Kara Walker, Taryn Simon, Andre Leon Talley, Alice Springs, Roxanne Lowit, Arthur Elgort, Sarah Harmarnee, Vincent Peters, Marcus Piggott & Matt Alas, Solve Sundsbo, Sarah Moon, Brana Wolf, Sam Taylor-Wood, Wolfgang Tillmans, Victoria Bartlett, Anne Christensen, Tom Hunter, Laurie Simmons, Jane & Louise Wilson, Adam Fuss, Sarah Morris, Tracey Emin, Karen Kilimnik, Beth B, Elke Krystufek, Anna Gaskell, Jeff Burton, Thomas Ruff, Richard Phillips, Mariele Neudecker, Rachel Lowe, Katrin Freisager, Trish Morrissey, Katy Grannan, Camille Bidault-Waddington, Charlotte Stockdale, Patrice Fuma Courtis, Karine Chane Yin, Marie Malterre, Paul Catling, Jerry Rockwell
    - Visionaire #30, The Game, 1999; VIS 14; Vuitton, Louis (Box 2)
      Includes designs by Nan Goldin, Alex Katz, Steven Klein, David LaChapelle, Mary Ellen Mark, Elizabeth Peyton, Karl Lagerfeld, Serge Lutens, M/M, Pierre Joseph, Richard Fauguet, Guy Limone, Ruben Toledo, Pedro Almodovar, Juan Gatti, Jordi Labanda, Miquel Barcelo, Layla D'Angelo, Maurizio Cattelan, Francesco Clemente, Luca Stoppini, Lorenzo Mattotti, Grazia Toderi, Armin Linke, Syd Mead, Takashi Murakami, Yoshitomo Nara, Daisuke Nakayama, Miwa Yanagi, Takashi Homma, Tracey Moffatt, Patricia Piccinini, Matthys Gerber, Rosemary Laing, Anna Zahalka, Lyndall Milani, Raymond Meier, Popilotti Rist, Francois Berthoud, Roman Signer, Olaf Breuning, Alexia Walther
    - Visionaire #31, Blue, 2000; VIS 15 (Box 10)
      Includes designs by Mario Testino, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Fabien Baron, Nan Goldin, Gus Van Sant, Mats Gustafson, Francois Berthoud, Wolfgang Tillmans, Steven Klein, Terry Richardson, Steve Hiett, Richard Burbridge, Lee Swillingham, Ellen Von Unwerth, Glenn Brown, Gary Hume, David Armstrong, Richard Phillips, Matt Alas & Marcus Piggott, Sharon Ellis, Greg Foley, Dietmar Busse, Mario Milizia, Patrick Ibanez, W. Wisniewski, Justine Kurland, Katy England, Karl Templer, Andrew Richardson, Edward Enninful, Patrice Fuma Courtis, Karine Chane Yin, Catherine Ayme, Stuart Spalding, Takaho Inoue, Orfi, Noki
    - Visionaire #32, Where?, 2000; VIS 16; Hermes (Box 3)
      "Includes designs by Oliver Wasow, Lauren Greenfield, Orfi & Greg Foley, Taryn Simon, Michael Roberts, Mario Testino, Armin Linke, Dan Macmillan, Hussein Chalayan, Jeff Burton, Karl Lagerfeld, Mats Gustafson, David Armstrong, Peter Lindbergh, Thomas Nutzl, Oliver Herring, Stephane Sednaoui, Me Company, Pedro Almodovar, M/M (Paris), Mary Ellen Mark, Michael Stripe, Raf Simons, Mario Testino, Manolo Blahnik, Philip Treacy, Angelica Blechschmidt, Kelly Klein, Daniel Klajmic, Wolfgang Tillmans, Jean-Paul Goude, Nadav Kander, Gregory Crewdson, Nan Goldin, Inez Van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, David Lachapelle, David Lasnet, Jean-Louis Dumas, Bruce Weber, Victoria Sambunaris, Andreas Gursky, Fabien Baron"
    - Visionaire #33, Touch, Fall-Winter 2000; VIS 17; Berthoud, Francois; Fendi (Box 11)
    - Visionaire #34, Paris Dior Homme Solitaire, 2000; VIS 18; Slimane, Hedi (Box 12)
      Includes designs by Hedi Slimane, Craig Kalpakjian, Axel Ebert, Elisabeth Ballet, Armin Kinke, 3Deluxem Myriel Milicevic, Andreas Angelidakis, Chris Habib, Lia Re-Move.org, Luisa Lambri, Solve Sundsbo, Golan Levinm, AIR & Nan Goldin & Jean-Benoit Ducknel, Stephane Dafflon, Domonique Perrault, Tom Kovac, Stephen Hendee, Martin Dorbaum, Finn Geipel, Yves Netzhammer, James Casebere, Kazuyo Sejima & Ryue Nishizawa, H5 & Yorgo, Neil Denari, Thomas Demand, John Maeda, Preston Scott Cohen, The Designers Republic, Chris Cunningham, Greg Lynn
    - Visionaire #35, Man, 2001; VIS 19; Testino, Mario (Box 2)
      Includes designs by Mario Testino, Slim Aarons, Miles Aldridge, Richard Avedon, David Bailey, Jonathan Becker, Paul Berends, Gary Boas, Thelma Vilas Boas, Gisele Bundchen, Richard Birbridge, Jeff Burton, Paul Cadmus, Helena Christensen, Larry Clark, Pedro Claudio, Liz Collins, Sofia Coppola, Cindy Crawford, Bonnie Cutrone, Bruce Davidson, Vincente De Paulo, Jonathan De Villiers, Sophie Delaporte, Horst Diekgerdes, Lucinda Douglas-Menzies, David Downtown, Warren Du Prez, Lukas Duwenhogger, Amy Eckert, Joel Elkins, Eve Fowler, Carmen Fruedenthal, Mary Frey, Sadie Frost, Tim Gardner, Nathaniel Goldberg, Douglas Gordon, Rene Gruau, Tim Hailand, Simon Henwood, Eva Herzigova, George Hurrell, Jade Jagger, Daffyd Jones, Greg Kadel, Bill King, Scott King, Daniel Klajmig, Nick Knight, Daniel Kramer, Marcelo Krasilcic, Jordi Labanda, Karl Lagerfeld, Salim Langatta, David Lasnet, Mark Leckey, Thomas Lenthal, Sam Levin, Roxanne Lowit, Sarah Lucas, Dan MacMillan, Pierluigi Macor, Will McBride, Andrew McKim, Donald MacPherson, Tracey Moffatt, Tim Noble & Sue Webster, Thomas Nutzl, Catherine Opie, Simon Periton, Vincent Peters, Raymond Pettibon, Elizabeth Peyton, Richard Phillips, Phil Poynter, Richard Prince, Sophy Rickett, Peter Robathan, Mick Rock, Ugo Rondinone, Luis Rosario, Jochem Sanders, Howard Schatz, Maurice Scheltens, Claudia Schiffer, Collier Schorr, Bob Seidman, Jeanloup Sieff, David Slijper, Rena Small, Carter Smith, Smythson of Bond Street, Lord Snowdon, Helen Soloman, Mario Sorrenti, Solve Sundsbo, Sam Taylot-Wood, Olga Tobreluts, Ed Van Der Elsken, Peter Van Straaten, James Vanderzee, Elle Verhagen, Raymond Voinquel, Tim Walker, Gillian Wearing, Richard Westall, Hype Williams, Tobin Yelland, Richard Young
    - Visionaire #36, Power, 2001; VIS 20 (Box 13)
    - Visionaire #38, Love, 2002; VIS 21; Tiffany & Co. (Box 4)
      Includes designs by Elsa Peretti, Hiro, Steven Meisel, Karl Lagerfeld, Mario Testino, Inez van Lamsweerde & Vinoodh Matadin, Nick Knight, Bjork, Matthew Barney, Craig McDean, Mario Sorrenti, Peter Lindbergh, Kylie Minogue, Amber Valletta, Destiny's Child, Helmut Newton, Francois Berthoud, Mats Gustafson, Nan Goldin, David Armstrong, Richard Philips, Tim Noble & Sue Webster, Philip Treacy, Elizabeth Peyton, Peter Saville, Dan Forbes, Christy Turlington, Ed van der Elsken, Setsuko Klossowska de Rola, Jean-Georges Vongerichten, Tobias Schweitzer, A. Canovas, Joyce Carol Oates, Kenneth Koch, Jonathan Safran Foer, T. Cole Rachel
    - Visionaire #39, Play, 2002; VIS 22 (Box 3)
      Includes designs by Mario Testino, Baz Luhmann, Steven Meisel, Pedro Almodovar, Karl Lagerfeld, Wong Kar Wai, Nick Knight, Spike Jonze, Craig McDean, Peter Lindbergh, Steven Klein, Tony Oursler, Darren Aronofsky, Roman Signer, Snorri Bros., Imaginary Forces & Greg Lynn
    - Visionaire #40, Roses, 2003; VIS 23; Sims, David (Box 14)
      Includes designs by David Sims
    - Visionaire #41, World, 2003; VIS 24 (Box 15)